Christopher Chandra

Address: Woolloongabba, QLD 4102

Mobile: 0432 644 477

Personal Website: christopherchandra.info Email: christopher chandra@outlook.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-chandra-9601bb1b9/

Github: https://github.com/ACHC30

Profile

Master's graduate Computer Science with skills in Web and Mobile Application Development, Object Oriented Programming, and scrum IT Project Management. QUT graduate with experience across various projects utilizing Agile methodology of Project Management. Strong knowledge in React, JavaScript and C# and a passion to work collaboratively with a team. Ability to consistently finish tasks with a high level of efficiency and keen to commence a career in Information Technology.

| _ | | | | | | • | | |
|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|
| _ | a | u | _ | ~ | • | | ^ | - |
| _ | | | | _ | | | | |
| _ | м | м | • | | | | v | |

| Education | |
|---|---------------------|
| ACS Professional Year Program in Computer Science/ICT Navitas Professional, Brisbane | Mar 2022 - Ongoing |
| Master of Information Technology - Computer Science Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane | Aug 2021 - Jul 2022 |
| Bachelor of Information Technology - Computer Science Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane | Jan 2020 - Aug 2021 |

Employment History

Tobacco SG, Everton Park, QLD

Sales Attendant Sep 2022 - Ongoing

- Demonstrate efficiency in financial transaction using POS with 0% error
- Exceed customer satisfaction with effective communication

Mitra Agung, Maumere, Indonesia

IT Freelancer Jan 2017 – Ongoing

- Establish effective data design and structure utilising Excel
- Manage the database using google drive for cost effective data storage
- Prototype solutions using third-party software

Christopher Chandra Page 1 of 4

Phone: 0432 644 477

Javier Garcia Lopez, Brisbane, QLD

IT Freelancer Contract

Sep 2023 - Oct 2023

- Establish Docker Compose connectivity with an AWS EC2 instance.
- Facilitate the deployment of both the backend and frontend systems on the client's computer.
- Contribute to the development of React JavaScript components for the frontend.
- Successfully resolve deployment-related system issues and bugs.

Javier Garcia Lopez, Brisbane, QLD

IT Freelancer Contract

Oct 2023 - Nov 2023

- Oversee backend deployment and AWS service management
- Implement server scaling through AWS Auto Scaling groups
- Utilize Amazon Relational Database Service for data storage
- Created project documentation

Degree Related Projects

QUT, IFN666 Assessment 2 Project

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a website designed to monitor and analyse stock market fluctuation using both financial modelling prep and alpha vantage APIs.
- Demonstrated skills in JavaScript front-end development
- Demonstrated proper use of API to get stock prices data and visualize them properly on the website.

QUT, IFN666 Assessment 3 Project

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a mobile app based on the IFN666 assessment 2 designed to monitor and analyse stock market fluctuation using both financial modelling prep and alpha vantage APIs.
- Demonstrated skills in React Native JavaScript
- Demonstrated proper use of API to get stock prices data and visualize them properly in the website.

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477

QUT, Blockchain-Based Assessment Ledger Website

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a website that exceed our client's requirements within a span of 6 months.
- Demonstrated skills in JavaScript front-end development
- Achieved success in testing SDN using Linux virtual OS
- Used Trello for quality control

QUT Foundry, Gamified Entrepreneur Dashboard

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a website that satisfied the client's requirements within a duration of 1 year
- Designed database using SQL
- Designed front end of the website with HTML and CSS
- Implemented back end of the website with Phyton
- Organized workflow using SCRUM method
- Documented the coding of the project
- Fixed bugs and troubleshoot the website

UBAYA University, Final Exams Scheduling Website

Jan 2018 - Jan 2019

University of Surabaya

- UBAYA University, Final Exams Scheduling Website Jan 2018 Jan 2019
- University of Surabaya, Christopher
- Designed the front-end using HTML

Key Skills

| Skills | | | | | |
|--|--|--|--|--|--|
| Technical Skills: | | | | | |
| Experience with AGILE scrum project management method | | | | | |
| Codes with a focus in object-oriented programming | | | | | |
| Ability to develop an Entity Relationship Diagram | | | | | |
| Soft Skills: | | | | | |
| Strong team working skills demonstrated via lack of negative outcomes when working collaboratively with a team Adaptability shown by being able to problem solve technical problems and work as front and back-end roles. Integrity shown by maintaining complete honesty with both my team and manager. | | | | | |
| | | | | | |

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477

Memberships

• Australian Computer Society (ACS) membership Member

Referees

Referees are available upon request

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477